<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">[ÑåVîĝåţé ĥöḿé one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">[ÑåVîĝåţé ûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">[Ḿöŕé öþţîöñš one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">[Çöļļåþšé one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description_format">[»%1$s«, »%2$s« one]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_subtitle_description_format">[»%1$s«, »%2$s«, »%3$s« one]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">[Šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">[Šéåŕçĥ… one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">[Šéåŕçĥ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">[Çļéåŕ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">[Šûɓḿîţ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">[νöîçé šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">[Çĥööšé åñ åþþ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">[Šéé åļļ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">[Šĥåŕé ŵîţĥ »%s« one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">[Šĥåŕé ŵîţĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">[999+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">[ÖÑ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">[ÖFF one]</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">[Šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="app_name">[ĻîVé éåŕţĥ ŵåļļþåþéŕš one two three]</string>
    <string name="globe_wallpaper_name">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕļð, Šöļåŕ Šýšţéḿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="globe_wallpaper_description">"[Îñšþîŕéð ɓý Åþöļļö 17'š βļûé Ḿåŕɓļé, Vîéŵ Éåŕţĥ ƒŕöḿ šþåçé ɓåšéð öñ ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ, ŵîţĥ ŕéåļ-ţîḿé çļöûðš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="sunset_wallpaper_name">[Ĥöŕîžöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="sunset_wallpaper_description">[Ļööķ ţö ţĥé ĥöŕîžöñ. Ţĥé šûñ ŕîšéš åš ýöûŕ þĥöñé çĥåŕĝéš, åñð ļöŵéŕš åš ţĥé ɓåţţéŕý îš ûšéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="whitehaven_wallpaper_name">[ŴĥîţéĥåVéñ βéåçĥ, qûééñšļåñð, Åûšţŕåļîå one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="whitehaven_wallpaper_description">[Ķñöŵñ ƒöŕ îţš ŵĥîţé šåñðš, ŴĥîţéĥåVéñ βéåçĥ îš ḿåðé ûþ öƒ 98»% pure« šîļîçå, ŵĥîçĥ ĝîVéš îţ å ɓŕîĝĥţ ŵĥîţé çöļöŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="kent_wallpaper_name">[Ĝåŕðéñ, Ķéñţ, Ûñîţéð Ķîñĝðöḿ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="kent_wallpaper_description">[Ŵîţĥ îţš åɓûñðåñçé öƒ ƒŕûîţ öŕçĥåŕðš åñð ĥöþ ĝåŕðéñš, Ķéñţ îš ķñöŵñ åš Ţĥé Ĝåŕðéñ öƒ Éñĝļåñð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="halfdome_wallpaper_name">[Ĥåļƒ Ðöḿé, Ýöšéḿîţé Ñåţîöñåļ Þåŕķ, ÇÅ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="halfdome_wallpaper_description">[Ţĥîš ĝŕåñîţé ƒöŕḿåţîöñ îñ Ýöšéḿîţé νåļļéý, ñåḿéð ƒöŕ îţš ðîšţîñçţ šĥåþé, ŕîšéš ḿöŕé ţĥåñ 4,737 ƒţ åɓöVé ţĥé Våļļéý ƒļööŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]</string>
    <string name="moab_wallpaper_name">[Åŕçĥéš Ñåţîöñåļ Þåŕķ, Ḿöåɓ, Ûţåĥ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="moab_wallpaper_description">[Îñ åððîţîöñ ţö å Våŕîéţý öƒ ĝéöļöĝîçåļ ƒöŕḿåţîöñš, ţĥé þåŕķ çöñţåîñš öVéŕ 2,000 ñåţûŕåļ šåñðšţöñé åŕçĥéš, îñçļûðîñĝ ţĥé ŵöŕļð-ƒåḿöûš Ðéļîçåţé Åŕçĥ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="togo_wallpaper_name">[Šĥîñĵûķû, Ţöķýö, Ĵåþåñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="togo_wallpaper_description">[Åţ 656 ƒţ ĥîĝĥ, ţĥîš ɓûîļðîñĝ îñ Šĥîñĵûķû, ðéšîĝñéð ɓý Ýöšĥîķåžû Ûçĥîðå, îš ţĥé 28ţĥ ţåļļéšţ ɓûîļðîñĝ îñ Ţöķýö åñð ţĥé 33ŕð ţåļļéšţ îñ Ĵåþåñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four]</string>
    <string name="pantheon_wallpaper_name">[Þåñţĥéöñ, Ŕöḿé, Îţåļý one two three]</string>
    <string name="pantheon_wallpaper_description">"[Åļḿöšţ ţŵö ţĥöûšåñð ýéåŕš åƒţéŕ ţĥé Þåñţĥéöñ ŵåš ɓûîļţ, ţĥé çîŕçûļåŕ ɓûîļðîñĝ ŕéḿåîñš ţĥé ŵöŕļð'š ļåŕĝéšţ ûñŕéîñƒöŕçéð çöñçŕéţé ðöḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="google_earth_live_earth_collection">[Ĝööĝļé Éåŕţĥ, ĻîVé éåŕţĥ šéŕîéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="live_earth_collection">[ĻîVé éåŕţĥ šéŕîéš one two three]</string>
</resources>
